

Corneliu Zediu BA of Eng. & Mmgt.

About Me

Corneliu Zediu Schwarenbergstraße 160 70184, Stuttgart

0049/15224019045 zediucorneliu@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://corneliu-zediu.developerakademie.net/portfolio/

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/corneliuzediu

Github: https://github.com/corneliuzediu

I am a junior front-end developer with diverse experience from engineering, sales and business administration. Having a liking since always for technology, I have committed to following a career in IT and web development. My best decision in this regard was to follow the Developer Akademie course in order to build a strong foundation in web development.

I am looking forward to building on my experience.

Main Stack:

- JavaScript.
- TypeScript, Angular, Material Design.
- HTML, CSS / SCSS, Bootstrap.

Side Stack:

- Git, APIs (REST), Google Firebase.
- Lightroom.

Skills

- Building applications with JavaScript & Angular: I built landing-pages and several web apps, as well as OOP-based Jump-and-Run-Games with the respective technologies.
- Working in a software-team: During learning coding, I did various group projects where I learned how to develop a software project in a team.
- RFID devices maintenance and team training. I was responsible for the good operation of store devices, as well as training and helping the employees in using them.
- Team leading and high sense of responsibility: Starting from the lowest job position, I learned the importance of team management and sense of responsibility that got me to an area supervisor position and section responsible position.

Professional Experience

Bershka Deutschland Gmbh / Salesman & Chico Respo

March 2019 - June 2022 - Bielefeld & Stuttgart, Germany

- Maintenance and repair of basic work devices.
- Visual merchandising and organizing the men section of the store.
- Responsibility for section KPI-report to management.
- Customer service in German, English & Romanian.
- Daily & weekly team tasks organization together with the management team.

Altius Fotovoltaics Srl / Economical Engineer

November 2017 - June 2018 - Bucharest, Romania

- Customer offers and service in English & Romanian.
- Operation of industrial machinery and equipment.
- Utility manual for the factory processes.

Cedar Fair Entertainment Company / General Area Supervisor

(June 2014 - October 2014) - (June 2017 - October 2017) - Sandusky, Ohio, USA

While in College, I took part in the "Work and Travel" Program and went for a couple of summers in Cedar Point, USA, where I got the chance to experience my first promotion transition. From cleaning attendant, to supervising a team and finishing with supervising the maintenance and cleaning group.

Education

Developer Akademie / JavaScript & Angular Web Development Training

July 2022 - April 2023 - Munich, Germany

Project based coding academy focused on front-end development, agile project management and building several projects in teams and alone via HTML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, Firebase.

"Vasile Alecsandri" University / Bachelor

2013 - 2017 - Bacau, Romania

Major with double degree: Mechanical Engineering and Management.

The major interconnected the production elements of a factory/company with the economical elements in order to provide the most efficient outcome.

"Ion Ghica" Economic Highschool

2009 - 2013 - Bacau, Romania

Fundamental of economics, business administration, health and safety and customer service.

Languages

Romanian: native

English: C1

German: B2